{"problem": "2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 17 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice. 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 45 dollars. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars. A lasagna at Bistro Nice and 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 41 dollars. The price of a Caesar salad at Urban Plate is the same as that of a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a lasagna at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Bistro Nice, Caesar salad at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate are: 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 45 dollars, 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 17 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice, the price of a Caesar salad at Urban Plate is the same as that of a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, a lasagna at Bistro Nice and 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 41 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars less than a creme brulee at Urban Plate. 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 44 dollars. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate and 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 66 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars less than a creme brulee at Urban Plate, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 44 dollars, 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate and 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 66 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars more than 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ. 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 37 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. A scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars more than 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ, 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 37 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. A Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 22 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate. 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 58 dollars. A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 81 dollars. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Urban Plate, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Urban Plate are: 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 58 dollars, a Cobb salad at Urban Plate costs 22 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate, 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 81 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place and 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 61 dollars. A scrambled egg at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 19 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place. 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 39 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 39 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 5 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 10 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 45 dollars. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 5 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 10 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 43 dollars. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 24 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate and a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 34 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Urban Plate are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 24 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate and a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 34 dollars, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 43 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ and 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 63 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Texas BBQ, pizza at Mike's Place, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ are: 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ and 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 63 dollars, 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 33 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate. A creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 26 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ and 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 28 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 10 dollars. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Texas BBQ are: a creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 26 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ, a Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 33 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate, a Greek salad at Texas BBQ and 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 28 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 17 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place. 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 17 dollars more than a pizza at Mike's Place. A burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. A burger at Mike's Place costs 31 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Mike's Place, pizza at Mike's Place, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine are: a burger at Mike's Place costs 31 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place, 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 17 dollars more than a pizza at Mike's Place, 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 17 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 36 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 54 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a pie at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Taste Good Cuisine are: a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 54 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. A burger at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ. 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 25 dollars more than 2 burgers at Urban Plate. A pizza at Urban Plate and a pizza at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Urban Plate, pizza at Texas BBQ, burger at Urban Plate, lasagna at Urban Plate are: a pizza at Urban Plate and a pizza at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars, a burger at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ, 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 25 dollars more than 2 burgers at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate. A pizza at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars. 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ and 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 42 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 25 dollars. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Texas BBQ are: a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 25 dollars, 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 45 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 12 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice. A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 21 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars. The price of 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a lasagna at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Texas BBQ, lasagna at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice are: a lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 21 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ, 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 45 dollars, 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 12 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice, the price of 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 25 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ. 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 38 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 13 dollars more than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ. 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 29 dollars more than 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Texas BBQ, burger at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ are: a burger at Texas BBQ costs 25 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ, 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 38 dollars, 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 13 dollars more than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ, 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 29 dollars more than 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars more than a pie at Urban Plate. A pie at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. A pie at Mike's Place and a burger at Mike's Place cost 23 dollars. A scrambled egg at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars. 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 22 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Mike's Place, burger at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Urban Plate are: a pie at Mike's Place and a burger at Mike's Place cost 23 dollars, 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 22 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 10 dollars more than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate. 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 10 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and a pizza at Urban Plate cost 47 dollars. The price of a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a pizza at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 10 dollars more than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and a pizza at Urban Plate cost 47 dollars, 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine, the price of a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 34 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice. A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate and 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 42 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 3 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate and 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 63 dollars. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Bistro Nice are: a scrambled egg at Urban Plate and 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 42 dollars, 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate and 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 63 dollars, a Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 34 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice, 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 3 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "2 pies at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice. 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars less than 3 pies at Urban Plate. The price of 2 pies at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice. A pizza at Bistro Nice costs 20 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice. A pizza at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Urban Plate, pie at Urban Plate, pizza at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Bistro Nice, pie at Bistro Nice are: 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars less than 3 pies at Urban Plate, 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice, a pizza at Bistro Nice costs 20 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice, the price of 2 pies at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 39 dollars. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars more than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 38 dollars. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Texas BBQ are: 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars more than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 38 dollars, 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 39 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate. 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate. A piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. 2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 33 dollars less than 3 burgers at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a burger at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, burger at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate are: 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, 2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 33 dollars less than 3 burgers at Bistro Nice, 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than a lasagna at Texas BBQ. 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 32 dollars more than a Greek salad at Texas BBQ. 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and a creme brulee at Bistro Nice cost 52 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, lasagna at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Bistro Nice are: 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and a creme brulee at Bistro Nice cost 52 dollars, 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 32 dollars more than a Greek salad at Texas BBQ, 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than a lasagna at Texas BBQ, 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Texas BBQ costs 17 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place. A pizza at Mike's Place costs 3 dollars more than a Greek salad at Texas BBQ. A Greek salad at Mike's Place and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 35 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 42 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Texas BBQ, pizza at Mike's Place, pizza at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ are: a pizza at Mike's Place costs 3 dollars more than a Greek salad at Texas BBQ, a pizza at Texas BBQ costs 17 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place, 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 42 dollars, a Greek salad at Mike's Place and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 35 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 34 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 8 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 11 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 10 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ are: 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 8 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 10 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 34 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. 2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate. A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate and a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost 22 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice. 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice are: 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice, 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ and a pizza at Urban Plate cost 39 dollars. A pizza at Texas BBQ costs a dollar less than a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ. A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ and a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate cost 19 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 7 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a pizza at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, pizza at Urban Plate are: a pizza at Texas BBQ costs a dollar less than a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ and a pizza at Urban Plate cost 39 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A burger at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 65 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 81 dollars. The price of 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place. 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, burger at Mike's Place are: 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 65 dollars, 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 81 dollars, the price of 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place, 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A burger at Texas BBQ costs 21 dollars less than 2 burgers at Mike's Place. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ and a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 25 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Mike's Place, burger at Texas BBQ, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, burger at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place are: a burger at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place, 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ, a burger at Texas BBQ costs 21 dollars less than 2 burgers at Mike's Place, 3 burgers at Texas BBQ and a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 25 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. 2 pies at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 58 dollars. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars less than 3 pies at Texas BBQ. A pie at Urban Plate costs 3 dollars less than 2 burgers at Texas BBQ. A pie at Texas BBQ and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Texas BBQ, burger at Texas BBQ, burger at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Urban Plate, pie at Urban Plate are: 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars less than 3 pies at Texas BBQ, 2 pies at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 58 dollars, a pie at Texas BBQ and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars, a pie at Urban Plate costs 3 dollars less than 2 burgers at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 31 dollars. 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice are: a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice, 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place, 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 31 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars more than 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place. A pizza at Mike's Place costs 4 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 25 dollars more than a pizza at Texas BBQ. 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 19 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Texas BBQ, pizza at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, Cobb salad at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ are: 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 25 dollars more than a pizza at Texas BBQ, a pizza at Mike's Place costs 4 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars more than 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place, 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 19 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 13 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Mike's Place. A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 13 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice and 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 37 dollars. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 11 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Mike's Place are: 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 13 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place, a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice and 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 37 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 2 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Urban Plate. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate and 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 40 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. The price of 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place is the same as that of 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: a scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 2 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Urban Plate, 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate, a scrambled egg at Urban Plate and 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 40 dollars, the price of 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place is the same as that of 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 41 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 29 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate. 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 23 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice. A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate. A creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice are: 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 29 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 41 dollars, a creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate, 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 23 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost a dollar less than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate. A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 11 dollars more than a lasagna at Bistro Nice. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, lasagna at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice are: 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost a dollar less than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice. 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 23 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine. A Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars less than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, burger at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 23 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars less than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, a burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 12 dollars more than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate. 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost a dollar more than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 23 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate. A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 21 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Urban Plate are: a lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 21 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice, 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 23 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate, 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost a dollar more than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A burger at Mike's Place costs 22 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. The price of a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice is the same as that of a burger at Mike's Place. A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 11 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 17 dollars more than a lasagna at Mike's Place. 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, burger at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, burger at Bistro Nice are: the price of a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice is the same as that of a burger at Mike's Place, a burger at Mike's Place costs 22 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place, 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place and 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 66 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 8 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place. 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 7 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place are: 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 8 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place and 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 66 dollars, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ, 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 7 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars more than 3 pies at Mike's Place. A pie at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars less than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ. 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 11 dollars more than 2 pies at Texas BBQ. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ and 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 66 dollars. A burger at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, pie at Mike's Place, pie at Texas BBQ, burger at Mike's Place are: a pie at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars less than a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 11 dollars more than 2 pies at Texas BBQ, 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars more than 3 pies at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ and a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost 40 dollars. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 72 dollars. A Greek salad at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 15 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ, 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 72 dollars, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ, 3 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ and a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost 40 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 35 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate and a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost 34 dollars. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine and a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars. 3 pies at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, pie at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Urban Plate are: 3 pies at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine and a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars, 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 35 dollars, 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate and a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost 34 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place and 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 78 dollars. 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 10 dollars more than a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine. A Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 48 dollars. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Mike's Place are: 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine cost 48 dollars, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 10 dollars more than a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place and 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 78 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars more than 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place. 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Mike's Place. A Caesar salad at Mike's Place and a pizza at Bistro Nice cost 20 dollars. 2 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 29 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice. A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, pizza at Bistro Nice, pizza at Mike's Place are: 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Mike's Place, 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars more than 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place, a Caesar salad at Mike's Place and a pizza at Bistro Nice cost 20 dollars, 2 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 29 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "2 Greek salads at Mike's Place and a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost 23 dollars. A pie at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars less than a fruit tart at Mike's Place. A pie at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 20 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Texas BBQ are: 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place and a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost 23 dollars, 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 20 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ, a Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 4 dollars less than a fruit tart at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. 3 pies at Bistro Nice and 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 66 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate. 3 pies at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars more than a lasagna at Bistro Nice. A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate and 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 27 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, pie at Urban Plate, lasagna at Bistro Nice are: 3 pies at Bistro Nice and 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 66 dollars, a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate and 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 27 dollars, 3 pies at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars more than a lasagna at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "The price of a creme brulee at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 2 burgers at Bistro Nice. A burger at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 54 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Mike's Place are: 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice, 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 54 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 burgers at Bistro Nice and 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 32 dollars. 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 pies at Urban Plate. 3 pies at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars less than 3 burgers at Urban Plate. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. The price of 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate is the same as that of 3 burgers at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Bistro Nice, burger at Urban Plate, pie at Urban Plate, Caesar salad at Urban Plate are: 3 pies at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars less than 3 burgers at Urban Plate, 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 pies at Urban Plate, the price of 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate is the same as that of 3 burgers at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 burgers at Urban Plate and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 13 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate. 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate. A Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 19 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a burger at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ, burger at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ are: 2 burgers at Urban Plate and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars, 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 2 burgers at Urban Plate, 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 19 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 13 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A pie at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 5 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 7 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate are: 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 7 dollars less than 3 pies at Bistro Nice, a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 5 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars less than a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice. 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than a lasagna at Bistro Nice. A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than a lasagna at Bistro Nice, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars less than 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 25 dollars more than a pizza at Urban Plate. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and a pizza at Texas BBQ cost 12 dollars. A pizza at Urban Plate costs 5 dollars. A pie at Urban Plate costs 15 dollars. 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 7 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a pizza at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, pizza at Texas BBQ are: 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 7 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and a pizza at Texas BBQ cost 12 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 20 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice. 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 21 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice. A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 16 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice. A fruit tart at Bistro Nice and 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 29 dollars. A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 11 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Urban Plate, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Urban Plate, lasagna at Bistro Nice are: 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 21 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice, a fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 20 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice, a fruit tart at Bistro Nice and 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 29 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars more than a lasagna at Texas BBQ. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ and 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 38 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, lasagna at Mike's Place are: 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars more than a lasagna at Texas BBQ, a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ and 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 38 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. A creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 10 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. A creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Mike's Place are: 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate, 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place. 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Urban Plate. 3 pizzas at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost 38 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost 23 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, pizza at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: 3 pizzas at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost 38 dollars, 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Urban Plate, 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost 23 dollars, 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice and 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 56 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 51 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice and a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars less than a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine are: a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars less than a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice and a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 16 dollars, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice and 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 56 dollars, 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 51 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 11 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice. 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place and 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 38 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 33 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place and 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 38 dollars, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 33 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A burger at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. The price of 2 burgers at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 54 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Mike's Place, burger at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, burger at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place are: a burger at Bistro Nice costs 2 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place, the price of 2 burgers at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice, a burger at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice, 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 54 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 Greek salads at Urban Plate and a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 57 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 35 dollars more than a Greek salad at Texas BBQ. 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. A Caesar salad at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 7 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate are: 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ, 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 35 dollars more than a Greek salad at Texas BBQ, 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 7 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate and a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 57 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A burger at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 31 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate. 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 48 dollars. The price of 2 burgers at Urban Plate is the same as that of 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate costs 10 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ are: 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 48 dollars, the price of 2 burgers at Urban Plate is the same as that of 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ, a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 31 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars more than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and a creme brulee at Mike's Place cost 28 dollars. A creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 42 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place are: 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and a creme brulee at Mike's Place cost 28 dollars, 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 42 dollars, 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars more than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Mike's Place and 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 28 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 10 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place and 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 45 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 21 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place, 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 pies at Urban Plate cost 5 dollars more than a fruit tart at Urban Plate. A pie at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars. A fruit tart at Urban Plate and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 25 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, pie at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Mike's Place are: a fruit tart at Urban Plate and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 25 dollars, 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 5 dollars more than a fruit tart at Urban Plate, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 16 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 39 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice and 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 31 dollars. 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 3 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Bistro Nice, burger at Bistro Nice, burger at Texas BBQ are: 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 16 dollars, a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 39 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice, 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 3 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, 2 burgers at Bistro Nice and 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 31 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 67 dollars. 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 15 dollars more than 3 pies at Mike's Place. 2 pies at Texas BBQ cost 22 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars less than a burger at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a pie at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Texas BBQ, burger at Mike's Place, pie at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, pie at Mike's Place are: 3 burgers at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 67 dollars, 2 pies at Texas BBQ cost 22 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place, a Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars less than a burger at Mike's Place, 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 15 dollars more than 3 pies at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 27 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ. 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice and 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 48 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Bistro Nice are: 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice and 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 48 dollars, 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 27 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 18 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 21 dollars more than a lasagna at Urban Plate. 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice and 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 38 dollars. A lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 32 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Urban Plate, lasagna at Bistro Nice, Caesar salad at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice are: 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice and 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 38 dollars, a lasagna at Bistro Nice costs 32 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice, 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 21 dollars more than a lasagna at Urban Plate, a Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 18 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Caesar salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice. A Caesar salad at Texas BBQ costs 11 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 14 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ and a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 19 dollars. A Caesar salad at Texas BBQ costs 34 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Bistro Nice are: a creme brulee at Texas BBQ and a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 19 dollars, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 14 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Caesar salad at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than 2 pizzas at Urban Plate. A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 15 dollars. 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ. 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 40 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Urban Plate, pizza at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Urban Plate are: 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than 2 pizzas at Urban Plate, 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ, 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 40 dollars, 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 8 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 28 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Urban Plate. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 29 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate and a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice cost 16 dollars. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 28 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 28 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate and a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice cost 16 dollars, a scrambled egg at Urban Plate and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 29 dollars, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 28 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 24 dollars more than a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 9 dollars less than 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars. 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 54 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a pie at Bistro Nice cost 39 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Bistro Nice are: 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine cost 9 dollars less than 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a pie at Bistro Nice cost 39 dollars, 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine cost 24 dollars more than a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 54 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 36 dollars. A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 14 dollars. A pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars. A pie at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars. 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars more than a burger at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a lasagna at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Texas BBQ, burger at Taste Good Cuisine, lasagna at Texas BBQ are: 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars more than a burger at Texas BBQ, 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 36 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 7 dollars more than a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine. A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 16 dollars less than 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ. 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Texas BBQ are: a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 16 dollars less than 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ, 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ, 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 7 dollars more than a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine cost 30 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 19 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 72 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 20 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Texas BBQ are: a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 19 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine cost 30 dollars, a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 20 dollars, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ and 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 72 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 69 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 54 dollars. A Caesar salad at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 62 dollars. 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ and a Caesar salad at Urban Plate cost 60 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 54 dollars, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 62 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 52 dollars. A creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars. The price of 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 12 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Mike's Place are: 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 52 dollars, the price of 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine, a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 26 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. A creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars. A pie at Taste Good Cuisine and a pie at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars. 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars more than 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs a dollar less than a pie at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: a pie at Taste Good Cuisine and a pie at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars, a Greek salad at Mike's Place costs a dollar less than a pie at Mike's Place, 3 pies at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars more than 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate and a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost 48 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice and 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 51 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 10 dollars. The price of 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice are: 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate and a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost 48 dollars, a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice and 3 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 51 dollars, the price of 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice is the same as that of 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A burger at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 39 dollars. 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 65 dollars. 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost 56 dollars. 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine. A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Mike's Place, burger at Mike's Place are: 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 65 dollars, a burger at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 39 dollars, 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost 56 dollars, 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Urban Plate and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 49 dollars. A pie at Mike's Place costs 11 dollars. A fruit tart at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate and 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 46 dollars. 2 burgers at Urban Plate and a pie at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate, pie at Urban Plate, burger at Mike's Place are: 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate and 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 46 dollars, 2 burgers at Urban Plate and a pie at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars, 3 burgers at Urban Plate and 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 49 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A burger at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 18 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice. 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice. A burger at Mike's Place costs 4 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 37 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, burger at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice are: 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 18 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, a burger at Mike's Place costs 4 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 37 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 19 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ. 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars more than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ. A creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. The price of 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 8 dollars more than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Texas BBQ, burger at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Texas BBQ are: the price of 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ, a burger at Taste Good Cuisine costs 19 dollars less than 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ, a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 8 dollars more than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars more than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place and 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 35 dollars. A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars. 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Mike's Place. A Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 29 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place. 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Mike's Place are: a Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 29 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place, 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 15 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Mike's Place, 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place and 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 35 dollars, 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Mike's Place and 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. A fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 5 dollars less than a fruit tart at Mike's Place. 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost a dollar more than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate. 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, fruit tart at Urban Plate, fruit tart at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Urban Plate, Caesar salad at Mike's Place are: 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost a dollar more than a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, a fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 5 dollars less than a fruit tart at Mike's Place, a fruit tart at Mike's Place and 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars, 2 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 13 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place. A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 24 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 10 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place. 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 45 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate are: 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 10 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place, 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 13 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place, 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate and a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 45 dollars, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 24 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 84 dollars. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs a dollar less than a fruit tart at Bistro Nice. 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice and a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 33 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 19 dollars more than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice are: 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 84 dollars, 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice and a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 33 dollars, a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs a dollar less than a fruit tart at Bistro Nice, 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 19 dollars more than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ and 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 37 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and a pizza at Texas BBQ cost 25 dollars. 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 16 dollars more than a lasagna at Urban Plate. A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 10 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 21 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a pizza at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Texas BBQ, lasagna at Urban Plate, pizza at Urban Plate, pizza at Texas BBQ are: 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ and 2 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 37 dollars, 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 16 dollars more than a lasagna at Urban Plate, 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and a pizza at Texas BBQ cost 25 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. A pizza at Bistro Nice costs 13 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 4 dollars less than 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice. A grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Urban Plate. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs a dollar more than a pizza at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, pizza at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Urban Plate, a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 4 dollars less than 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice, a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs a dollar more than a pizza at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place. A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 5 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 17 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Mike's Place. 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 12 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ are: 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place, 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 17 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Mike's Place, 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 12 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 4 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 16 dollars more than 2 pizzas at Urban Plate. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 54 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 22 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, pizza at Urban Plate, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 54 dollars, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 16 dollars more than 2 pizzas at Urban Plate, 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 4 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 8 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 10 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate. 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ and 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 69 dollars. A fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 3 dollars less than a Greek salad at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ are: a fruit tart at Urban Plate costs 3 dollars less than a Greek salad at Texas BBQ, 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ cost 10 dollars more than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ, a Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 6 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate, 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ and 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 69 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ. 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ and a Caesar salad at Urban Plate cost 42 dollars. A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate. A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Urban Plate are: 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ, 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ and a Caesar salad at Urban Plate cost 42 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Caesar salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place. A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 7 dollars. A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars more than 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place. A piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, pizza at Mike's Place are: a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 24 dollars, a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Mike's Place.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 10 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. A burger at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 36 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place. 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place and a burger at Taste Good Cuisine cost 36 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine cost 27 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place and a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine cost 27 dollars, a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 36 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place, 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 10 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place and a burger at Taste Good Cuisine cost 36 dollars.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Bistro Nice and a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost 19 dollars. A pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 29 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. A pie at Bistro Nice costs 10 dollars. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 40 dollars. A Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars less than 2 pies at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Bistro Nice, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine are: a pizza at Bistro Nice and a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost 19 dollars, a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 40 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine and a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost 32 dollars. A Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 33 dollars. A Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. A pizza at Urban Plate costs 9 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Urban Plate are: a Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 33 dollars, 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine and a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost 32 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate. 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 34 dollars more than a Greek salad at Urban Plate. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 10 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 38 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate are: 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 34 dollars more than a Greek salad at Urban Plate, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 10 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 15 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A pie at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars less than 2 pies at Bistro Nice. A pie at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars less than 3 burgers at Bistro Nice. A piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars. 2 pies at Bistro Nice cost 21 dollars less than 3 burgers at Texas BBQ. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 5 dollars less than 2 pies at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a burger at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Texas BBQ, pie at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, burger at Texas BBQ, burger at Bistro Nice are: a pie at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars less than 2 pies at Bistro Nice, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 5 dollars less than 2 pies at Texas BBQ, 2 pies at Bistro Nice cost 21 dollars less than 3 burgers at Texas BBQ, a pie at Bistro Nice costs 9 dollars less than 3 burgers at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 5 variables but only 4 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. A Caesar salad at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 17 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Mike's Place. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ and 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 33 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 47 dollars. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ are: a Greek salad at Texas BBQ and 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 33 dollars, 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 47 dollars, 2 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ cost 17 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Caesar salad at Texas BBQ."}
